So the way you want to approach it is, you actually want to attack the front foot with the ball.
So what is, I mean, attacking the front foot?
So basically you want to position the ball towards that area, the area of the front foot, okay?
Pretend that you're actually going to go one way, and then actually, while he's distracted or while he's coming at you, the moment that he's ready to stop to defend or to start moving backwards, then you pass the ball through his legs, and then you go around him as....as you receive the ball on the other end.
So again, we are attacking the front foot.
Why the front foot?
Because that's where his weight is, and it's more difficult for him to turn this way to try to stop me, okay?
But at the same time, because we know that he's going to have his legs open, okay, and I'm going to take advantage of that, I want to put right between his legs, the ball goes through the legs, and I run to the side, because I know he will have a harder time catching me.
Okay?
So if you want to have some fun with it, you can start with your friends, you know.
Pretend that at a park, you know, let 'em do it.